Finding Aid for the William Ridley Wills II Post Card Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
William Ridley Wills II Post Card Collection
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0705
- Wills Postcards
  - Vanderbilt
    - Vanderbilt University, Main Bldg. Nashville, Tenn., 1901 (Folder 1)
    - 5782. Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn. “11/4/05 Here’s To Where All Those Who Have the ‘Mon’ Can Obtain It.” To: Miss Rose Shell, No 614 Cypress Street. Chattanooga, Tenn., 1905 (Folder 2)
    - Nashville, Tenn. Main Building, Vanderbilt University, 1906 (Folder 3)
    - *Sigilium Universitatis Vanderbiltiae* MDCCLXXIII*, 1907 (Folder 4)
    - Kissam Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., 1907 (Folder 4)
    - Nashville, Tenn. Kissam Hall- Vanderbilt University. To: Miss Maud Martin, Blackford, KY, 1908 (Folder 5)
    - Vanderbilt University, Department of Dentistry. Founded in 1879 by W.M.H. Morgan, M.D., D.D.S., Dean, 1908 (Folder 6)
    - Nashville, Tenn. College Hall- Vanderbilt University. Tuck’s Post Card, 1908 (Folder 7)
    - Kissam Hall, Vanderbilt, Nashville, Tenn., 1908 (Folder 8)
    - Vanderbilt University, NASHVILLE, TENN. (20729), 1909 (Folder 9)
    - MEDICAL COLLEGE, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY, NASHVILLE, TENN. A. Nickel, Pharmacist, Ash and Cherry St., 1911 (Folder 10)
    - Top-“A FALL OF THE BEAUTIFUL” ON CAMPUS, AT VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY, NASHVILLE, TENN. Bottom- IN DEAR OLD WINTER, AT VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY, COMMODORE VANDERBILT’S STATUE IN BACKGROUND., 1911 (Folder 11)
    - Furman Hall and main Building, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., 1911 (Folder 12)
    - Main Building, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., 1912 (Folder 13)
    - 12025, Furman Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., 1913 (Folder 14)
    - Vanderbilt University, Main Building, Nashville, Tenn., 1913 (Folder 15)
    - Furman Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., 1914 (Folder 16)
    - WALK LEADING FROM FURMAN HALL TO COLLEGE HALL, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY, 1919 (Folder 17)
    - VANDERBILT vs. MICHIGAN. South’s Greatest Spectacle. Seats Selling Fast. Admission: $2.00 and $1.50. Make Reservations Now. Openings New Stadium: SAT. OCT. 14, 1922 (Folder 18)
    - FURMAN HALL AND MAIN BUILDING, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY, NASHVILLE., 1923 (Folder 19)
    - Furman Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn. - 61, 1926 (Folder 20)
    - Medical Department, Vanderbilt University, South Campus, Nashville, 1929 (Folder 21)
    - Old Tower, College Hall, Vanderbilt University, Welcome to Nashville; During Home-Coming Week; 1931; September 19-26, 1931 (Folder 22)
    - COLLGE HALL, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY, NASHVILLE, TENN., 1936 (Folder 23)
    - KIRKLAND HALL. Vanderbilt University. Nashville, Tennessee, 1941 (Folder 24)
    - 6–Vanderbilt University, Kirkland Hall, Nashville, Tenn., 1942 (Folder 25)
    - Vanderbilt Hospital, Nashville, Tenn., 1944 (Folder 26)
    - Vanderbilt University Stadium- Nashville, Tenn. – 97, 1944 (Folder 27)
    - School of Medicine and Hospital, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn. Photo by 165th Photo Section Air Corps, Tenn. Nat, Guard, Nashville., 1951 (Folder 28)
    - Kirkland Tower and friend–Looking west from the 1957 Kissam Dormitories., 1957 (Folder 29)
    - Vanderbilt Hospital, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn. – 59, 1959 (Folder 30)
    - Joint University Library, Nashville, Tenn., 1960 (Folder 31)
    - Furman Hall, Vanderbilt University-Nashville- Tenn–61, 1961 (Folder 32)
    - Furman Hall- Vanderbilt University- Nashville- Tenn–61, 1961 (Folder 33)
    - Dudley Field and Memorial Gymnasium, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., 1967 (Folder 34)
    - Vanderbilt Hospital- Vanderbilt University- Nashville, Tenn. – 78, 1978 (Folder 35)
    - To: Ridley Wills, 4428 Warner Pl. Nashville 37205, 1980 (Folder 36)
    - SNOW SCENE ON VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY CAMPUS, SHOWING COMMODORE VANDERBILT’S STATUE IN DISTANCE, NASHVILLE, TENN., Not-dated (Folder 37)
    - STATUE OF COMMODORE, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY, NASHVILLE, TENN., Not-dated (Folder 38)
    - NASHVILLE, TENN. Scene Near Chancellor’s Residence, Vanderbilt University., Not-dated (Folder 39)
    - Greetings from Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 40)
    - Vanderbilt University By Night, Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 41)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 42)
    - Wouldn’t Our Grandfathers Stare if they could see NASHVILLE now? Vanderbilt University, Not-dated (Folder 43)
    - 6–Vanderbilt University, Kirkland Hall, Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 44)
    - Vanderbilt University- College Hall- Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 45)
    - Vanderbilt University, Kirkland hall, Nashville, Tennessee., Not-dated (Folder 46)
    - Kirkland Hall Vanderbilt University Nashville, Tennessee, Not-dated (Folder 47)
    - Vanderbilt University, College Hall, Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 48)
    - “Proudly stands our Alma Mater, as the years roll by…” In this campus view, the entrance to the Student Center, in Alumni Memorial Hall, appears in the foreground, and the clocktower of Kirkland Hall rises high against the sky., Not-dated (Folder 49)
    - Kirkland Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., home of the Commodores. Kirkland Hall is the Administration Building for Vanderbilt University., Not-dated (Folder 50)
    - KIRKLAND HALL. Vanderbilt University. Nashville, Tennessee., Not-dated (Folder 51)
    - KIRKLAND HALL. Vanderbilt University. Nashville, Tennessee., Not-dated (Folder 52)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN 37240, KIRKLAND HALL. Main administration building of the University. Completed in 1875. Named for Vanderbilt’s second chancellor James H. Kirkland, and his wife. Burned in 1905 and rebuilt. Restoration of the building was begun in 1982. Photo by John Halliburton.; Not-dated (Folder 53)
    - Benson Science Hall, Vanderbilt University. Photo by Will and Deni McIntyre., Not-dated (Folder 54)
    - Kirkland Hall Tower. Vanderbilt University. Photo by Will and Deni McIntyre., Not-dated (Folder 55)
    - Vanderbilt University campus with Kirkland tower in the background. Photo by Will and Deni McIntyre., Not-dated (Folder 56)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN. 37240, KIRKLAND HALL; Not-dated (Folder 57)
    - 12026. Kissam Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 58)
    - Vanderbilt University, Kissam Hall, Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 59)
    - Kissam Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Not-dated (Folder 60)
    - Kissam Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn.–29, Not-dated (Folder 61)
    - 7893. Kissam Hall, Vanderbilt University, showing West Nashville in the distance. Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 62)
    - Kissam hall, Observatory and Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 62)
    - Kissam Hall, Vanderbilt University., Nashville, Tenn.; Not-dated (Folder 63)
    - Kissam Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Not-dated (Folder 64)
    - THE LARGEST PLANT IN THE WORLD IN LOCATED AT NASHVILLE. KISSAM HALL, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY, NASHVILLE. NASHVILLE–THE POWDER CITY OF THE WOLRD., Not-dated (Folder 65)
    - FURMAN HALL, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY; NASHVILLE, TENN.; Not-dated (Folder 66)
    - Furman Hall, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tennessee., Not-dated (Folder 67)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN 37240, FURMAN HALL houses the humanities. Built in 1907, named for Francis Furman, Nashville dry-goods merchant. Remodeled in 1967. Photo by John Halliburton.; Not-dated (Folder 68)
    - JOINT UNIVERSITY LIBRARY, NASHVILLE, TENN., Not-dated (Folder 69)
    - 41–Joint University Library, Nashville, Tenn., Peabody College, Scarritt College, Vanderbilt University; Not-dated (Folder 70)
    - THE JOINT UNIVERSITY LIBRARY, NASHVILLE, TENNESSEE; The Joint University Library is operated by Peabody University, Scarritt College, and Vanderbilt University. It is the first co-operative University Library project established in America.; Not-dated (Folder 71)
    - Neely Auditorium Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tennessee; Not-dated (Folder 72)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN 37240, NEELY AUDITORIUM, home of the Vanderbilt University Theatre. Was an auditorium for University assemblies until converted to a theatre in 1976. Photo by Gerald Holly.; Not-dated (Folder 73)
    - Vanderbilt Hospital, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., Not-dated (Folder 74)
    - VANDERBILT HOSPITAL- VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY- NASHVILLE, TENN.- 78, Not-dated (Folder 75)
    - Vanderbilt Hospital, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tennessee, The Vanderbilt University School of Medicine and Hospital consists of a series of nine buildings brought together under one roof. This group of adjoining units contains the laboratories of the departments of the Medical School, lecture rooms, administrative offices, library and various subdivisions of the hospital. They also include the large department for out-patients and 200 beds.; Not-dated (Folder 76)
    - THE VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF MEDICINE AND HOSPITAL, Not-dated (Folder 77)
    - THE VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF MEDICINE AND HOSPITAL, Nashville, Tennessee; Not-dated (Folder 78)
    - THE VANDERBILT SCHOOL OF MEDICINE AND HOSPITAL, Nashville, Tennessee; Not-dated (Folder 79)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN 37240, Doorway of GODCHAUX HALL, Vanderbilt School of Nursing. Named for Mary Ragland Godchaux. Photo by Gary Gore.; Not-dated (Folder 80)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN 37240, OLIN HALL OF ENGINEERING. Built in 1974 with funds from the Olin Foundation, to house chemical engineering and materials science. Photo by John Halliburton.; Not-dated (Folder 81)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN 37240, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL; Not-dated (Folder 82)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN 37240, COMPUTER CENTER. 1963. A unit of the Stevenson Center for the Natural Sciences. Houses the DECSYSTEM-1099 computer system for use by the students, faculty, and administration. Photo by Gerard Holly.; Not-dated (Folder 83)
    - Vanderbilt University, Ariel view of Vanderbilt University Campus, showing the women’s dormitory, Branscomb Quadrangle in the foreground; Not-dated (Folder 84)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN 37240, MARGARET AND HARVY BRANSCOMB QUADRANGLE, named for Vanderbilt’s fourth chancellor and his wife. Dining hall and four connected dormitory buildings: LUPTON, VAUGHN, STAPLETON, and SCALES houses, named for four early Vanderbilt women. Photo by Gerald Holly.; Not-dated (Folder 85)
    - TOLMAN HALL. Dormitory. Named for Herbert Cushing Tolman, professor of Greek, founder of the Vanderbilt chapter of Phi Beta Kappa and dean of the College of Arts and Science from 1914 to 1923. Photo by Gerald Holly., Not-dated (Folder 86)
    - DIVINITY SCHOOL QUADRANGLE. Classrooms, offices, refectory, Benton Chapel (named for Dean John Keith Benton who led the school from 1939 until his death in 1956). Financed by University funds and a number of gifts., Not-dated (Folder 87)
    - BENTON CHAPEL, a part of the John Frederick Oberlin Divinity quadrangle. Oberlin College Graduate School of Theology merged with Vanderbilt Divinity School in 1966. Chapel is named for John Keith Benton, Divinity School Dean 1939-56., Not-dated (Folder 88)
    - OWEN GRADUATE SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT is named for Lulu Hampton Owen and Ralph Owen of Nashville Mechanical Engineering Hall, built in 1888 and now listed in National Register of Historic Places, has been incorporated into the modern (1982) Owen School complex. Photo by J. Clark Thomas., Not-dated (Folder 89)
    - THE OLD GYM. Built in 1880, a gift from William H. Vanderbilt, son of the University’s founder. Listed in the National Register of Historic Places. Interior of the original building was remodeled in 1961 to house the Department of Fine Arts Gallery. Photo by Gerald Holly., Not-dated (Folder 90)
    - BUTTRICK HALL. Built in 1928 and named for Wallace Buttrick, an officer of the General Education Board. Houses the Department of General Biology. Photo by Gerald Holly., Not-dated (Folder 91)
    - STUDENT UNION BUILDING. Student Union Building houses Cafeteria, Snack Shop, Book Store and recreational facilities., Not-dated (Folder 92)
    - GODCHAUX HALL. 1925. School of Nursing. Named for Mary Ragland Godchaux. A $1,000,000 under-ground addition was completed in 1978., Not-dated (Folder 93)
    - KISSAM QUADRANGLE, Not-dated (Folder 94)
    - DORMITORY, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY. NASHVILLE, TENN., Not-dated (Folder 95)
    - ALUMNI MEMORIAL HALL. Recreation and assembly rooms for students and faculty. Given by Alumni as a memorial to 44 Vanderbilt men who gave their lives in World War 1., Not-dated (Folder 96)
    - RAND HALL, VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY. Main dining hall of the University, campus bookstore and post office. This building was named for Frank Chambless Rand, 1898, president of the Board of Trust from 1935 to 1949. Alumni and other friends contributed about half the cost., Not-dated (Folder 97)
    - LINE UP OF VANDERBILT FOOTBALL TEAM OF, Not-dated; 1906 (Folder 98)
    - DUDLEY FIELD. Home of the Vanderbilt Commodores. Built in 1922, the stadium was renovated and expanded in 1982, now seats 41,135 spectators. Photo by J. Clark Thomas., Not-dated (Folder 99)
    - Dudley Field and Memorial Gymnasium, Vanderbilt University–Nashville, Tenn.; Not-dated (Folder 100)
    - BLAIR SCHOOL OF MUSIC was merged with Vanderbilt University in 1981. Established in 1964 through a bequest of Valere Blair Potter in memory of her mother, Myra Jackson Blair, the school was first a division of Peabody College. Private institution from 1977 until merger with Vanderbilt. Photo by John Halliburton., Not-dated (Folder 101)
    - STATUE OF COMMODORE CORNELIUS VANDERBILT by Italian sculptor Giuseppe Moretti stands in front of Kirkland Hall, at entrance to Vanderbilt University campus. Commodore Vanderbilt gave a million dollars in 1873 to build and endow the University, with the wish that it would “contribute to strengthening the ties which should exist between all sections of our common country.” Photo by Sallie India Linebaugh., Not-dated (Folder 102)
    - Spring Arrives on Campus, Not-dated (Folder 103)
      Dogwoods in bloom brighten our 3300acre grounds in early spring, heralding the longer, warmer days to come in Nashville.
    - AN OASIS IN THE CITY, Not-dated (Folder 104)
      Vanderbilt University’s lush landscape mixes towering trees, winding paths, and spacious lawns with historic and current architecture.
    - 24. Nashville: With Flounces, garlands, and pointed toes, these children danced at a Vanderbilt reunion in 1925., Not-dated (Folder 105)
    - 26. Nashville: “The Campus” grill is still on 21st Avenue South across from the Vanderbilt campus., Not-dated (Folder 106)
    - 25. Nashville: Professor Walter Storer photographed this fire destroying Vanderbilt’s Wesley Hall, 19 February 1932., Not-dated (Folder 107)
    - Aerial View- Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tennessee; Not-dated (Folder 108)
    - Vanderbilt University. The Commodore’s Statue. Nashville citizens subscribed to pay for the statue of the University’s founder, Commodore Cornelius Vanderbilt. It was installed on campus in 1897 and faced east. In 1949, the Commodore “turned around” to face north when the main entrance to the campus was placed on West End Avenue., Not-dated (Folder 109)
    - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN 37240, Not-dated (Folder 110)
      Tennessee General Assembly dedication to Mr. Vanderbilt- Photo by Will and Deni McIntyre.
    - Statue of Commodore Cornelius Vanderbilt, Not-dated (Folder 111)
      Vanderbilt University is a private, comprehensive teaching and research university with undergraduate, graduate, and professional programs. It has over 1,600 full-time faculty and diverse student body of about 9,700. Vanderbilt was founded in 1873 with a gift from Commodore Cornelius Vanderbilt.
    - KIRKLAND HALL, Not-dated (Folder 112)
      Kirkland Hall’s bronze bell sounds the hours from its distinctive tower. Named in 1939 for James H. Kirkland, Vanderbilt’s second Chancellor, the building houses administrative offices including the office of the Chancellor.
    - Cornelius Vanderbilt Statue up close, Not-dated (Folder 113)
    - Proposed Graduate School of Management–To open in 1970., Not-dated (Folder 114)
    - Vanderbilt University. Kirkland Hall clock tower., Not-dated (Folder 115)
    - Entrance to Vanderbilt Campus., Not-dated (Folder 116)
      NASHVILLE, TENNESSEE
      Statue of Cornelius Vanderbilt
    - Postcard of Kirkland Hall. VANDERBILT. Nashville, Tennessee., Not-dated (Folder 117)